A racing second hand, a shooting comet!
Sebuah tangan kedua yang cepat, komet jatuh yang kecil.
Conan's logic is good medicine for hearts tired by modern society!
Logika Conan bisa menyembuhkan hati yang kering oleh masyarakat modern.
Today's case is a "traverse"!
Kasus hari ini adalah sebuah "lintas".
Look it up and you'll find a zigzag hike!
Carilah dan kau akan menemukan dakian zigzag.
He sees the single truth for what it is,
Dia melihat satu-satunya kebenaran.
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
Memiliki penampilan seorang anak kecil dengan kepintaran orang dewasa.
His name?
Namanya adalah Detektif Conan!
Bus Accident! Kindergartener Killed! CEO Murdered!!
"Kecelakaan bis! Anak TK terbunuh! CEO terbunuh!"
The CEO of a quick-loan company was murdered, Bus Accident! Kindergartener Killed! CEO Murdered!!
CEO dari sebuah perusahaan pinjaman cepat dibunuh
and one child perished when a school bus was caught in the accident. Bus Accident! Kindergartener Killed! CEO Murdered!!
dan satu anak tewas ketika bis sekolah terlibat dalam kecelakaan itu.
The man who ordered the murder has been arrested!
Pria yang memerintahkan pembunuhan itu telah ditangkap.
He appears to have had a debt-related grudge.
Dia tampaknya memiliki dendam terkait hutang.
The murder was done by an unknown pro hitman known as the "Fox."
Pembunuhan dilakukan oleh seorang pembunuh bayaran pro
Investigations have been futile, and his whereabouts are unknown.
Penyelidikan sia-sia dan keberadaannya tidak diketahui.
I'm at the scene of the kindergartener's death six months ago.
Aku berada di tempat kejadian kematian anak TK itu enam bulan yang lalu.
The man responsible, the "Fox," is still at large, and the police--
Pria yang bertanggung jawab, "Fox" masih berkeliaran,
Dad. You have a client.
Ayah, kau ada klien.
Client!
Klien!
Shut up... Don't yell...
Diam. Jangan teriak.
He's already here.
Dia sudah di sini.
Sorry for showing up so suddenly.
Maaf karena tiba-tiba muncul.
Not at all...
Tidak sama sekali.
F-Find the hitman and keep him from killing?!
Temukan pembunuh bayaran dan cegah dia membunuh?
I may not look it,
Aku mungkin tidak terlihat begitu,
but I'm president of a Kansai real estate agency branch.
tapi aku presiden dari cabang agensi real estate Kansai.
Ushio Bunzo (40) Real Estate Branch President but I'm president of a Kansai real estate agency branch.
"Bunzo Ushio (40)" -Ketika aku melakukan pemeriksaan
health check five days ago,
kesehatan perusahaan lima hari yang lalu,
they mistook a simple ulcer for stomach cancer! Ushio Bunzo (40) Real Estate Branch President
mereka salah mengira maag biasa sebagai kanker perut.
I overheard the doctor and nurse,
Aku mendengar dokter dan perawatnya,
so I was really shocked when I heard it was cancer!
jadi aku sangat terkejut ketika aku dengar itu adalah kanker!
So don't tell me you... hired a hitman to kill you?
Jangan bilang kau mempekerjakan seorang pembunuh bayaran untuk membunuhmu?
Yes. The Fox.
Ya. Fox itu.
Fox?!
Fox?
But I only realized the mistake after I used my various work contacts
Tapi aku baru menyadari kesalahan itu setelah aku berusaha keras
to get in touch with him.
untuk berhubungan dengannya.
My money transfer had been deposited,
Pengiriman uangku sudah disetorkan
and his always-changing internet addresses had been closed out.
dan alamat internetnya yang selalu berubah sudah ditutup.
Even if I could contact him, it wouldn't be until a month later--
Meskipun aku bisa menghubungi dia, itu bisa hingga sebulan kemudian.
basically, I can't contact him while he's out to kill me!
Pada dasarnya, aku tak bisa menghubungi dia selagi dia mau membunuhku.
I see. So that's why you came to the great Mori Kogoro.
Begitu. Jadi itu sebabnya kau datang pada Kogoro Mouri yang hebat.
But are you being serious?
Tapi apa kau serius?
This isn't some hidden camera thing, is it?
Ini bukan semacam candaan kamera tersembunyi, bukan?
What?! Are you saying you can't trust me?!
Apa? Apa kau tak bisa mempercayaiku?
No, I do!
Tidak, aku percaya!
Look out!
Awas!
Bullets! Stay down!
Peluru! Menunduk!
That damn Fox...
Fox sialan itu...
Damn! He got away!
Sial! Dia lolos!
It looks safe now.
Tampaknya aman sekarang.
Oh, man...
Astaga.
Oh! What a big wallet! What's this?
Hah? Dompet yang besar!
It's nothing!
Bukan apa-apa!
What was that?
Apa itu tadi?
Damn. We gotta call the police.
Sial. Kita harus menelepon polisi.
No!
Tidak!
I hired a killer to kill me!
Aku mempekerjakan seorang pembunuh untuk membunuhku!
They wouldn't think too fondly of that!
Mereka takkan suka dengan itu!
No police!
Jangan ada polisi!
Please! I beg you! I'll even pay for your windows!
Tolong! Aku mohon padamu! Aku akan membayar untuk jendelamu!
Yeah, okay. I'll take the case.
Yah, baik. Aku akan terima kasusnya.
Really, detective?!
Benarkah, detektif?
Allow the great Mori Kogoro to catch the deadly Fox
Ijinkan Kogoro Mouri yang hebat untuk menangkap Fox itu
that's given the police so much trouble!
yang telah sangat merepotkan polisi!
Great!
Bagus!
Whoa, are you sure about this?
Hei, apa kau yakin tentang ini?
But how are you gonna catch the Fox?
Tapi bagaimana kau akan menangkap Fox?
You don't know what he's like, right?
Kau tidak tahu seperti apa rupanya, bukan?
Don't worry about that!
Jangan cemaskan itu.
The truth is, I included a condition with it!
Sebenarnya aku memasukkan syarat dengan itu.
I asked him to kill me while I'm on one of my beloved traverse trips!
Aku meminta dia untuk membunuhku
Traverse?
Lintas?
You mean like a trek up a mountain ridge?
Maksudmu seperti trek di pegunungan?
It's dangerous by the window. Let's talk over here.
Berbahaya dekat jendela. Mari bicara di sini.
R-Right.
Benar.
There's definitely something more to this guy...
Pasti ada sesuatu yang disembunyikan pria ini.
Tanbara Mountains
"Pegunungan Tanbara"
The next day, we set out on a traverse up the Tanbara Mountain ridge. Tanbara Mountains
Keesokan harinya, kami melakukan perlintasan
The next day, we set out on a traverse up the Tanbara Mountain ridge.
di punggung Gunung Tanbara.
This feels great!
Ini terasa menyenangkan!
Take a picture, Conan-kun!
Mari ambil foto, Conan.
We're gonna run out of film before we even go hiking, Ran-neechan.
Kita akan kehabisan film sebelum kita pergi mendaki, Ran.
We'll be fine! Here, let's get one together!
Jangan khawatir. Ayo kita berfoto bersama!
Hey, Dad! Take our picture!
Hei, Ayah! Ambil foto kami!
Ugh! We're not here for fun, you know!
Ya ampun. Kita bukan ke sini untuk bersenang-senang, kau tahu!
Here, Dad!
Ini, Ayah.
You guys understand, right?!
Kalian mengerti, bukan?
Of course! We're here to make it look like you're an ordinary hiker!
Tentu saja! Kita di sini untuk membuatmu tampak seperti pendaki biasa.
Which means we'll seem suspicious if we don't take pictures!
Yang artinya kami akan tampak mencurigakan jika kami tidak berfoto-foto.
Oh, right.
Oh, benar.
Oh, man...
Astaga.
Shortly after, we filled out the hiking forms at the office
Sesaat setelahnya, kami mengisi formulir pendakian di kantor
at the base of the mountain.
di dasar gunung.
They faxed the number of hikers and their names to a mountain lodge
Mereka mengirimkan fax informasi para pendaki ke sebuah penginapan gunung
so they could prepare our meals and such before we stayed the night.
agar mereka bisa menyiapkan makanan dan sebagainya sebelum kami menginap.
Let's see... Here we go, the mountain lodge.
Mari kita lihat. Ini dia, penginapan gunungnya.
We're staying the night here.
Kita akan bermalam di sini.
It's a route for experts, so you better be ready!
Itu rute untuk para ahli, jadi kau sebaiknya siap.
You too, Ran-neechan!
Kau juga, Ran.
Oh, what's with that tone?
Ada apa dengan nada itu?
Hey there! Is this your first time?
Hei! Apa ini kali pertamamu?
Hirai Kenichi (22) Toto Univ. Hiking Club I'm Hirai. I'm in my college's hiking club.
"Kenichi Hirai (22)" -Aku Hirai.
So you can count on me!
Jadi kau bisa mengandalkanku.
Great! We appreciate the help!
Bagus! Kami hargai bantuannya.
Hey, now. He could be the Fox, you know!
Hei, sudah. Dia mungkin adalah Fox.
I'm Ran! Oh, and this is my little brother, Conan!
Aku Ran! Dan ini adalah adikku, Conan.
Oh, uhh...
Begitu.
And this is my father!
Dan ini ayahku.
I'm from Tokyo. My name's Mori--
Aku dari Tokyo. Namaku Mouri...
Moriyama!
Moriyama.
I'm Ushio, from Kansai! Good to know you!
Aku Ushio, dari Kansai. Senang mengenalmu!
Nice to meet you!
Senang bertemu denganmu!
Well then, let's all go cheerily!
Baiklah, ayo kita semua pergi dengan riang.
I work for a real estate agency. How about you?
Aku bekerja untuk sebuah agensi real estate. Bagaimana denganmu?
W-What does it matter?! Takanashi Wataru (50) Company Exec
"Wataru Takanashi (50)" -Apa pentingnya itu?
Given these clouds, the weather might change.
Melihat awan-awan ini, cuaca mungkin berubah.
I'll give the mountain lodge a call.
Aku akan menelepon penginapan.
Does he have a thing for you?!
-Apa dia punya sesuatu untukmu? -Apa?
The Fox is apparently left-handed.
Fox itu tampaknya kidal.
He's thrown all his knives with his left hand.
Dia melempar pisaunya dengan tangan kirinya.
Take a look at that man there.
Lihatlah pria di sana.
He's left-handed!
-Dia kidal. -Benar.
Oh, Gramps? This is Hirai. I'll be staying again tonight!
Oh, Kakek? Ini Hirai.
Umm, Moriyama-san, was it? Have we met somewhere before?
Moriyama, bukan?
I'm Nose Shingo. I write novels. Nose Shingo (35) Novelist
Aku Shingo Nose. Aku menulis novel.
Oh, wow! I'm so happy to meet one of my very few readers!
Wow! Aku sangat senang bertemu salah satu dari pembacaku!
You read it too, didn't you, Conan-kun?
Kau juga membacanya, bukan, Conan?
Y-Yeah.
Yah.
It was about a killer with amnesia, if I'm not mistaken.
Tentang seorang pembunuh dengan amnesia, jika aku tidak salah.
I recall the trick being pretty lame...
Aku mengingan triknya cukup payah.
We haven't missed the check-in time, have we?!
Kita belum melewatkan waktu masuknya, bukan?
Please add us to the list, too!
Tolong tambahkan kami ke daftar itu juga!
Looks like it's gonna be a pretty big group...
Sepertinya itu akan menjadi grup yang cukup besar.
Saegusa Kyoko (25) Hiker We don't know the way,
"Kyoko Saegusa (25)" -Kita tidak tahu jalannya,
so I hope you don't mind us coming along. Saegusa Kyoko (25) Hiker
jadi kuharap kau tak keberatan kami ikut serta.
No, not at all!
Tidak, tidak sama sekali.
Come to think of it, we don't know the Fox's gender for sure.
Dipikir-pikir, kita tidak tahu jenis kelamin Fox.
It could be a woman!
Mungkin dia seorang wanita.
Sorry to keep you waiting! I'm Kawabe! It's nice to meet you!
Maaf membuatmu menunggu!
And so the traverse began.
Dan perlintasan dimulai.
Assuming the Fox is going to strike in this limited time and space,
Berasumsi Fox akan menyerang dalam waktu dan tempat yang terbatas ini,
he's either waiting in the mountains for his chance, like a guerilla,
entah dia menunggu di pegunungan untuk kesempatannya seperti gerilya
or he's one of the hikers.
atau dia salah satu dari para pendaki.
In short, there's a good chance one of the other five people is the Fox!
Singkatnya, ada kemungkinan satu dari lima orang itu
Be careful, it's slippery here!
Hati-hati, di sini licin.
There you go.
Aku tolong kau.
Please hold onto the rope.
Tolong berpegangan pada tali.
Watch out!
Awas!
Are you all right, Ushio-san?!
Apa kau baik-baik saja, Ushio?
How dare you...
Beraninya kau...
W-What are you doing?!
Apa yang sedang kau lakukan?
You did that on purpose!
Kau sengaja melakukan itu!
No! This snapped on its own! See!
Tidak. Ini putus sendirinya. Lihat!
It was all old and worn out.
Itu sudah tua dan usang.
Don't scare me like that!
Jangan menakutiku seperti itu.
T-That's my line!
Seharusnya aku yang mengatakan itu!
When I consider the Fox being one of the traverse members...
Aku mempertimbangkan Fox itu menyamar jadi salah satu pendaki,
...everyone seems a likely suspect!
tapi semua orang tampak seperti tersangka.
Those two really seem suspicious.
Mereka berdua tampak sangat mencurigakan.
Him, too.
Dia juga.
He's been glaring like crazy this whole time.
Dia melotot seperti orang gila selama ini.
He looks like he has something against Ushio-san.
Dia tampak seperti dia punya sesuatu terhadap Ushio.
Plus he was way ahead before, but now he's with us...
Ditambah, dia tadi sudah jauh di depan, tapi sekarang dia bersama kita.
Hey, you two.
Hei, kalian berdua.
Whatcha talkin' about? Are you people-watching?
Apa yang kalian bicarakan? Apa kalian mengawasi orang?
N-No, we're just...
Tidak, kami hanya...
Nothing happened after that,
Tidak ada yang terjadi setelah itu,
as we approached the final rest spot before our lodging for the night.
begitu kami mendekati peristirahatan akhir sebelum penginapan malam ini.
What?
Apa?
Nothing... You just seem full of energy...
Tidak apa-apa. Kau hanya tampak penuh energi.
Of course I am! I'm in shape because of my karate training!
Tentu saja! Aku bugar karena pelatihan karateku.
Want to try out a leg technique?
Ingin mencoba teknik kaki-ku?
No, that's okay.
Tidak, tak apa-apa.
Say, where's that college guy?
Di mana anak kampus itu?
Probably taking a rest somewhere.
Mungkin dia sedang istirahat di suatu tempat.
Or he ran off 'cause his cover got blown!
Atau dia kabur karena penyamarannya terbongkar.
They said the cover's been blown!
Mereka bilang penyamarannya terbongkar.
Keep quiet! Let's go!
Diam! Ayo kita pergi.
There seems to be something to those two...
Sepertinya ada sesuatu pada mereka berdua.
H-Help! Someone!
Tolong! Seseorang!
Hurry! Someone!
Cepat! Seseorang!
What's going on?!
-Apa yang terjadi? -Di bawah sana...
Down there...
Di bawah sana...
Hirai-san!
Hirai!
Why? Why Hirai-san...
Kenapa? Kenapa Hirai...
So it wasn't him?
Jadi bukan dia?
You did this!
Kau yang melakukan ini!
You threw him over, didn't you?!
Kau melempar dia, bukan?
L-Let go! Don't touch me!
Lepaskan! Jangan sentuh aku!
Stop!
Berhenti!
Shouldn't we hurry down there and take a look?
Bukankah kita seharusnya bergegas ke bawah sana dan melihat?
Oh, right!
Oh, benar!
Poor guy...
Pria malang.
He had to have died instantly...
Dia pasti tewas seketika.
Hey, you. Don't be wandering around. It's dangerous.
Hei, kau. Jangan berkeliaran.
A knife! There's a little blood on it!
Sebuah pisau! Ada sedikit darah di atasnya!
What?! A knife?! D-Don't tell me the Fox did this!
Apa? Pisau?
But he doesn't have any stab marks...
Tapi dia tidak memiliki luka tikam.
This mark!
Tanda ini...
Ah!
Begitu.
Look! This cut looks like the knife grazed him!
Lihat! Luka ini tampak seperti pisau menggores dirinya.
And the fact that the knife is lying there...
Dan fakta bahwa pisau ini tergeletak di sana
...means he dodged a knife the killer threw...
artinya dia menghindari sebilah pisau yang pembunuhnya lemparkan
...but he lost his footing and fell off the cliff...
tapi dia kehilangan keseimbangan dan jatuh dari tebing.
So he intended to kill him?
Jadi dia berniat untuk membunuhnya?
You! Where've you been?!
Kau! Kemana saja kamu?
I've been around.
Aku berkeliling.
The hell you have!
Kau berbohong!
I went on ahead, but came back when I heard screaming.
Aku pergi dulu,
I mean, those guys seem pretty fishy if you ask me...
Maksudku, mereka tampak cukup mencurigakan.
What?! Them?!
Apa? Mereka?
Screw this! These people are nothing but trouble!
Sial! Orang-orang ini benar-benar menyebalkan!
Let's get going!
Ayo kita berangkat.
Hold it! We're all going to wait at the mountain lodge!
Tunggu! Kita semua akan menunggu di penginapan gunung.
I must ask you all to stay with us until the police arrive.
Aku meminta kalian untuk tetap tinggal dengan kami hingga polisi tiba.
Screw that! W-What gives you the right to do that?!
Sial! Apa yang memberimu hak untuk melakukan itu?
Whoever leaves a murder scene will seem all the more suspicious.
Siapapun yang meninggalkan tempat kejadian
Damn!
Sial!
Moriyama-san. You seem quite accustomed to this. What's your job?
Moriyama, kau tampak cukup terbiasa dengan ini.
Oh, I, uh...
Aku...
He's an office worker! Right, Dad?
Dia seorang pegawai kantor. Benar, Ayah?
Y-Yeah, that's right!
Yah, itu benar!
An office worker, huh?
Seorang pegawai kantur?
He definitely doesn't look like it...
Dia jelas tidak tampak seperti itu.
Rain!
Hujan!
Let's hurry!
-Ayo cepat! -Ya! Semakin gelap!
Dry yourselves off. You'll filthy up the cabin. Iwata Jukichi (60) Cabin Manager
"Juukichi Iwata (60)" -Keringkan diri kalian.
Are you the manager of this cabin, old man?
Apa kau manajer kabin ini, pak tua?
Yes. Come inside, already! You'll catch cold!
Ya. Masuklah! Kau akan kena flu!
Whew...
Whew...
I'm exhausted...
Aku lelah.
Dad. Aren't you going to call?
Ayah. Apa kau takkan menelepon?
Oh, right.
Oh, benar.
I'm gonna use the phone, mister.
Aku akan menggunakan telepon, pak.
What the-- I'm not even getting a tone! Umm--
Apa? Aku tidak mendengar nada apapun! Permisi.
The lines probably got knocked out during all that lightning earlier...
Salurannya mungkin terputus selama kilat tadi.
Happens all the time.
Ini selalu terjadi di sini.
Now, what? It's raining, it's night...
Sekarang, apa? Hujan, sudah malam...
It's dangerous to go down mountains at night! I'd advise against it!
Berbahaya untuk menuruni gunung di malam hari.
Not to mention this is the summit. There are no other cabins nearby.
Belum menyebutkan ini adalah puncaknya.
Meaning we're pretty much completely isolated.
Artinya kita terisolasi.
You can't be serious!
-Tidak mungkin! -Kau pasti bercanda!
Murderer?
Pembunuh?
One of our companions was murdered in a fake accident.
Salah satu rekan kita dibunuh dalam kecelakaan palsu.
A fake accident?
Kecelakaan palsu?
Tarnishing these mountains like that... how shameful!
Mencoreng pegunungan ini seperti itu... sungguh memalukan!
Anyway, the killer could be in this very room.
Bagaimanapun, pembunuhnya mungkin berada di ruangan ini.
Who knows? Maybe it was you, Ushio-san.
Siapa yang tahu? Mungkin itu kau, Ushio.
S-Say what?!
Apa?
It's common sense in mysteries that the killer is the least likely person.
Umum dalam misteri bahwa
Rubbish! I'm starving! Food!
Omong kosong! Aku lapar! Bawakan kami makanan!
Curry Rice
"Nasi Kari"
This... is dinner?
Ini makan malam kami?
What do you want? We're in the mountains.
Apa yang kau inginkan? Kita di pegunungan.
What's wrong?
Ada apa?
Oh, nothing.
Oh, bukan apa-apa.
What is this feeling of strangeness?
Apakah perasaan aneh ini?
Something's not right!
Ada yang tidak beres.
What could it be?!
Apakah itu?
What do you think's wrong with Takanashi-san?
Menurutmu apa yang salah dengan Takanashi?
He knows what he's done.
Dia tahu apa yang telah dia lakukan.
You really did...
Ini benar-benar kau yang melakukannya.
N-No!
Tidak!
D-Don't kill us!
Jangan bunuh kami!
What nonsense! Everyone carries hunting knives when hiking!
Omong kosong! Semua orang membawa pisau berburu ketika mendaki.
T-That's true, but...
Itu benar.
I remember now! Moriyama-san!
Aku ingat sekarang! Moriyama, kau adalah...
You're Mori Kogoro-san, the great detective, aren't you?!
Kogoro Mouri, detektif hebat itu, bukan?
D-Detective?!
Detektif?
D-Don't tell me...
Jangan bilang padaku...
What's with the false name? Are you on some sorta case?
Mengapa kau menggunakan nama palsu?
Personal reasons? Or... could it have to do with this murder?
Alasan pribadi? Atau mungkinkah terkait dengan pembunuhan ini?
Sheesh! How long is it going to rain?
Berapa lama lagi hujannya akan berhenti?
What's the forecast got in store?
Apakah ramalan cuacanya?
You can tell me in secret. C'mon.
Kau bisa memberitahuku diam-diam. Ayolah.
Now for the next news item.
Sekarang untuk berita berikutnya.
This morning, Tanaka Yoro, 60, was fatally stabbed in Tanbara Village,
Pagi ini, Yoro Tanaka, 60 tahun,
and the suspects may have fled into the Tanbara Mountains.
dan para tersangka mungkin telah kabur ke Pegunungan Tanbara.
Police and fire departments have a 50-man team searching the area.
Ada 50 orang dari kepolisian yang melakukan pencarian di area tersebut.
Oh, come on! I can't sleep like this!
Oh, ayolah! Aku tak bisa tidur seperti ini!
Look out!
Awas!
What the--?!
Apa?
Dad?!
Ayah!
Someone just left!
Seseorang baru pergi!
What's going on?
Apa yang terjadi?
Takanashi-san is gone!
Takanashi pergi!
I knew it was him!
Aku tahu itu dia.
Damn you! You can't get away from us!
Sial! Kau tak bisa kabur dari kami!
Be careful! You're the one he's after!
Hati-hati! Kau yang dia incar.
Let's go!
Ayo kita pergi!
Someone!
Tolong!
Takanashi-san!
Takanashi!
What was that?
Apa itu tadi?
Help! Help me!
Tolong! Tolong aku!
H-H-Help!
Tolong!
Watch out, Conan!
Awas, Conan!
It's the Fox!
Itu Fox!
Wait! Something's not right!
Tunggu! Ada yang tidak beres.
T-The ceiling's falling!
Atapnya jatuh!
The walls are closing in! I'm scared! I'm scared!
Dindingnya menutup! Aku takut...
Help me!
Tolong aku!
H-Huh?
Hah?
I think he might have claustrophobia.
Aku rasa dia mungkin mengidap klaustrophobia.
Claustrophobia?
Klaustrophobia?
Meaning that's why he rushed out of the cabin?
Artinya itu sebabnya dia bergegas keluar dari kabin?
Yeah. And he came here to avoid the rain, but then it happened again.
Yah. Dan dia datang ke sini untuk menghindari hujan,
Which means he's...
Yang artinya dia...
...not the Fox...
Bukan Fox.
Some land sharks once held me captive.
Beberapa rentenir pernah mengurungku.
I got them mad when I refused to sell my land.
Aku membuat mereka marah ketika aku menolak untuk menjual tanahku.
I've been afraid of cramped places ever since...
Aku takut tempat-tempat sempit sejak itu.
So that's also why you don't like the real estate guy!
Jadi itu juga sebabnya kau tidak suka pria real estate itu.
Good call, kid.
Bagus, nak.
But that means the Fox is still on the loose!
Tapi itu artinya Fox itu masih berkeliaran.
Which one of the other four is the hitman?!
Siapa dari empat orang itu pembunuh bayarannya?
That was Ran!
Itu tadi suara Ran!
The Fox is in this room. And he's the one behind these murders!
"Episode Selanjutnya" -Fox ada di ruangan ini.
C-Come again?!
-Apa? -Pembunuh bayaran?
The Fox?!
Fox?
Yes! The peerless hitman, the Fox, the one behind these incidents...
Ya. Pembunuh bayaran, Fox, dalang di balik insiden-insiden ini...
...is you, the novelist, Nose Shingo!
adalah kau, novelis, Shingo Nose!
R-Really?!
Benarkah?
Damn you!
Sial!
W-What are you doing?!
Apa yang sedang kau lakukan?
On the next Conan: "The Traverse of Terror Murder Case (Part 2)."
Selanjutnya dalam Conan,